freedownloadsarchive.com 2001-04-26

# G A M E X T A Z Y . C O M

**  
Privacy Statement for Gamextazy**

**Gamextazy** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Gamextazy

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. 

**Advertisers**  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

**Personal Information**  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Gamextazy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
